- What are you talking about?
- You forget what Penny did to you?
(Raj:)It took you two years and defiling my
sister to turn that frown upside down.
(Leonard:)I didn't defile your sister,
we had a relationship.
(Raj:)I heard you call her Brown Sugar.
(Raj:)In my book that's defilement.
- You wanna know my opinion?
- Oh, boy, do I.
(Sheldon:)Sarcasm?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)All right, then.
(Sheldon:)The reason you're fixated on
a good-natured simpleton like Penny...
(Sheldon:)...is that she's the exact opposite
of your first romantic attachment...
(Sheldon:)...your brilliant, yet intimidating,
mother.
(Leonard:)Where on earth did you get that from?
(Sheldon:)It's in her book
Needy Baby, Greedy Baby.
(Leonard:)That doesn't make it true.
(Sheldon:)It's called non-fiction for a reason,
Leonard.
See you Iater.
If they make a movie version
of that book...
(Raj:)...you know who should play
Leonard's mother? Sandra Bullock.